Jhal Hello Hello
everyone the plan we are
reviewing today is your Future
Generali's Super Saver Health Insurance
Plan this plan has some unique features
like if you don't take the policy last year
then you can get a discount of up to 80% next year
discount up to 80% and
you can make pregnancy claim
even after the ninth and apart from this there are some
unique features which we will cover in this video the
engine will be joint venture Future
Group General Insurance Company Future Group
Indian company is very famous in retail
their hot Big Bazaar and Food Bazaar
Extra is definitely
Quietly's insurance company which
comes in the top ten insurance companies of the world and is a very good company their
headquarter is in Mumbai let's
start the review of the plan this plan has two
variants home explain the second variant
health super saver so explain if we
talk about the sum insured range then in this you
can take a policy of up to ₹50 lakh
entries are 2 years and maximum entries are 17 years child
Entries First Day
Cover which can be covered in the policy for different styles for up to 25 years. If we take
Real Life
Long Home then
two adults and four children can be
covered in this policy and two different parents
and two dependents parents in law. Free
hospitalization is 6 days in this and post
hospitalization Neel Devi Dark Treatment.
This means any such treatment
for which you need to stay in hospitalization for 24 hours.
You
can go home after getting your treatment done which is 2018.
Talking about expenses, you
can add in this even after nine days which can be
appointed on the screen of the organization. This
treatment i.e. Ayurveda treatment
Siddha Unani and Homeopathic are
covered in this plan. The condition in this is
that it should be treatment from a government approved
center.
Treatment should be done in a government hospital only.
Organ Donor is covered for 7 days in this policy.
It is to be kept in mind
that whoever donates an organ does
not have the subscription of emergency
ambulance. 100% hospitalization cover
treatment in this.  Now Square Subscribe is a very
unique feature, let's talk about it. If you
subscribe and do not make a claim in the first year, then you
can get up to 80% discount in the next year.
On renewal from For Health, in the Explain
option, if you do
not make a claim on the policy for the first 2 years, then you
can get a discount of up to 80% on the policy for the next two years,
but if any claim comes in those 2 years, then
you will not get the discount. This is a very
unique feature which can save us a lot of money.
In this policy, the company
gives you the option to pay your premium
on installment mode, in which
if you take monthly, then you will have to pay
14% extra if you take extra water and if you
take more, then you will have to pay 3% extra.
Subscribe, you
can do it by paying extra cost,
by selecting the double option,
you will have to pay 10% extra loading,
after which if you subscribe for some time, then
you will have to pay 30% extra if you
subscribe, then it gives you the option to
remove the deposit
plus seat medical  Checkup: If you
are below 50 years and you select less than 20 lakhs
then there will be no medical checkup.
If you subscribe for medical checkup, there will be a request in this. If you are
above 50 years of age, you can
also select MS Word, then you will get a
medical checkup.
If you are found fit in the medical, then the
company will give you the policy, otherwise your money will be
refunded and whatever tests you have
charged are
reimbursed to you up to 100%. If the policy
underwriting decides, it should be done
from the listed center of the appointed company and this should be done
within the maximum period. Your
tests will be done for 30 days only. If
any disease is found then underwriting sometime
extra. But you have to keep in mind
that even after whatever you do,
you will have to complete the waiting period for subscribing for this disease. For
example, if you have a sugar
problem and the company
gives you a policy by adding loading, then you will
get sugar related claim only after 2 years, which is applicable to you if you
subscribe in this policy.  You
can check the first option
Standard Deduction, in this the pregnancy
claim is Rs.
15000 for normal and Rs. 25000 for cesarean
delivery in three to four policies, you can click on it, whereas in six
policies you
can deliver for Rs. 25000 for normal and Rs. 35000, but I can claim Rs. 30000 for normal and
Rs. 45000 for delivery or for delivery
that on a policy of Rs. 15 lakh,
whether it is normal or
cesarean, you can claim Rs. 50000, whether it is normal or cesarean, you can click on the policy of Rs. 20 lakh,
phase subscription November delivery
and Rs. 1 lakh delivery,
apart from this you can check in the subscription,
you
can also take the limitations of mental subscription, in this you have
different limitations in the double option, again we are
putting different limitations on the screen, you can check it,
you can get a little extra claim in it,
but in this you have to pay,
if you absolutely need it, we are putting that also
on the screen, you can check that also,
now let's talk about optional sub  The limit
of Rs 3 lakh is being put on the screen available at the time,
please check it,
in this your option for replacement
subscription can be applied, if you want then
that is also being put on the screen, you
can check it, General Appointed 5,000 plus
hospital on the channel, if you are
not able to get treatment from a hospital equipped with series, then
you will have to
inform the company about your situation and within 15 days,
if you do not like the company's policy, then
you have a free look period,
you can also cancel the policy,
if you still miss it then you will get the
subscription after one month, if
you are subscribed then you will not
get anything, subscribe, if you liked the video
then subscribe
to our channel because we keep bringing more, thank you
for watching